{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What does HTML stand for?",
      "correctAnswer": "Hypertext Markup Language",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "Hotmail ",
        "How To Make Language"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "True or false: all HTML documents must start with a document type declaration",
      "correctAnswer": "True",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "False"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the 'p' tag used for?",
      "correctAnswer": "creating a paragraph",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "creating a partition",
        "creating a new page"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of tag is used to define an HTML link?",
      "correctAnswer": "anchor tag",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "link tag",
        "url tag"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not an attribute of an image tag?",
      "correctAnswer": "image-border",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "alternative text",
        "source file"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the <ul> tag stand for?",
      "correctAnswer": "unordered list",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "underline",
        "unused link"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following will produce the largest default heading font?",
      "correctAnswer": "h1",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "h2",
        "h3"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "True or false: All HTML elements must close with an ending tag.",
      "correctAnswer": "False",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "True"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does href refer to?",
      "correctAnswer": "the URL or web address for a link",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "image file path",
        "HTML reference"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "How many default headings are defined in HTML?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "3",
        "5"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which HTML element is metadata stored in?",
      "correctAnswer": "head element",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "body element",
        "footer element"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "True or false: a web browser recognizes extra white space within a paragraph tag",
      "correctAnswer": "False",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "True"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which tag is used to preserve both spaces and line breaks?",
      "correctAnswer": "pre tag",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "p tag",
        "spaces tag"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What attribute allows you to use in-line CSS on an HTML element?",
      "correctAnswer": "style",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "in-line CSS",
        "CSS-active"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What HTML defines removed or strike-through text?",
      "correctAnswer": "del",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "cross-out",
        "strike-through"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "True or false: You can only use text as links in HTML?",
      "correctAnswer": "False",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "True",
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the default display marking for a list item?",
      "correctAnswer": "bullet point",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "dash",
        "none"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a valid block element?",
      "correctAnswer": "image element",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "list element",
        "header element"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a valid inline element?",
      "correctAnswer": "script",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "article",
        "figure"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which tag defines a block-level section in a document?",
      "correct_answer": "div",
      "wrongAnswer":[
        "span",
        "canvas"
      ],
      "tags": ["HTML"]
    },
  ]
}
